怎么了
What is it?
没什么  我不知道要吃什么
Nothing. I can't find anything that I want to eat.
吃什么都会让我恶心
Everything makes me nauseous.
我告诉你  怀孕可不像吃蛋糕那么简单  哇啊  蛋糕
I'm telling you, being pregnant is no piece of cake. Oh, cake.
不行
No.
真可怜  天啊
Aw, honey, I'm sorry. God.
什么香味  是浴室传出来的
Ooh, what is that smell? It's coming from the bathroom.
你倒是多了些怪癖
Wow, pregnancy does give you some weird cravings.
是我  菲比
Yeah. It's me. It's Phoebe.
听着  这里有我想吃的东西  什么
Listen, there's something in here I want to eat. What?
什么味道这么香
What smells so good?
是洗发香波吗  是石榴香味
Is it the shampoo? It's guava.
不是
No.
等下  等等
Ugh. Oh, wait, wait.
是我的红肠三明治吗
Is it my bologna sandwich?
对  对  没错
Yes, yes, yes.
这孩子居然想吃红肠  可能他想让我吃肉
I can't believe it. The baby wants bologna. The baby wants me to eat meat.
我不能吃肉  等等
I can't eat meat. Uh, wait, wait.
也许是腌黄瓜
Maybe it's the pickle.
老友记  第四季  第16集  假派对
Friends S04E16  The One With The Fake Party
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
（中央咖啡馆）
你在写什么
What are you writing?
约书亚明天要来
Well, Joshua's coming in tomorrow...
因为我没胆儿约他出来
...and since I don't have the guts to ask him out...
所以我打算卖他件衣服   然后把这纸条塞进口袋里
...I'm gonna sell him a coat and put this note in the pocket.
是吗  是
Oh, yeah? Oh.
"约书亚  有空打电话给我  你这样的男人…
"Joshua, give me a call sometime. Guys like you...
…永不过时"
...never go out of style."
你都扔了哪些话啊
What did you throw away?
伙计们  嗨  你们干什么去了
Hi, guys. Hey, what have you guys been up to?
我们去Cupert-Hewitt博物馆  看维多利亚时期门把展
Oh, we went to see a collection of Victorian doorknobs at the Cooper-Hewitt museum.
没带-我
Without me?
是我舅舅拖我们去的   结果很有意思
My uncle dragged us there, but actually it turned out to be interesting.
是啊  那些门把很华丽
Yeah. They were so ornate and beautiful.
我是说  你们看
I mean, look at that.
我不知道英国的国情
I don't know how museums work in England...
但这里  不能顺手牵羊
...but here, you're not supposed to take stuff.
这是礼品部的
I, uh... I got it from the gift shop.
那里没什么防盗措施
They have really lax security there.
开个玩笑
It's a joke.
拜
Bye.
制片: 塔德史帝文斯
我该走了  再见  我会想你们的  拜拜
Right, I've got to be off. I'll see you. Bye-bye, then.
再见
Bye.
看起来你们相处得很愉快嘛
Wow. Hey, you guys seem to be having a good time.
对啊  她人很棒   而且很有趣
Oh, yeah, she is amazing, and she's so much fun.
还有  你知道吗  跟她在一起时  我也相当有趣
And you know what? When I'm with her, I'm fun.
我甚至报名学开直升机
I even signed up for helicopter classes.
她过两天就走了  我其实不用这样
She's leaving in two days. I don't have to do it.
过两天  你一定很失落吧  是啊
Aw, two days? You must be bummed. Yeah.
她非回伦敦不可
She's got to go back to London.
但你知道吗  我一开始就有心理准备
But you know what? I've been prepared for this from the start.
我们都知道我们彼此只有这两星期  仅此而已
We both knew we had two weeks together and then that's it, you know?
我的每段恋情也都是这样
Hey, that's what all my relationships are like.
对  但是罗斯他们是"双方"都知道  只有两星期而已
Yes, but in Ross' case, they both know in two weeks that's it.
菲比  嗨
Pheebs, hey.
宝宝  好啊  好啦  我知道
Hello, hello. Yeah, I know. Yeah.
这孩子就喜欢肉
So the baby is totally craving meat.
下午我想用素汉堡骗骗他
This afternoon, I tried tricking it.
我做了个素汉堡  就是让他以为他吃到肉了
I made it a soy burger so that maybe it'd think it was getting meat.
然后  我又恶心了
You know? And I got nauseous.
也许是因为素汉堡太难吃
Well, maybe that's because soy burgers suck.
怀孕吃东西真难啊
Being pregnant is hard on your tummy.
但你有一种孕妇的光彩
Hey, but at least you got that cool, pregnant-lady glow.
真好听  你要是吐一个早上也会红光满面的
Oh, that's sweat. You throw up all morning, you'll have that glow too.
这是你想要的风衣
Okay. Uh, here's that trench coat you wanted.
太好了
Oh, great. Great.
很舒服
Wow, yeah, it's comfortable. Yeah.
这个可以用来装变态
Man, you could really flash somebody in this thing.
不行  出了店门
Ha, ha. They don't want you to put your hands in the pockets...
才能把手放进口袋里
...until you are out of the store.
为什么
Why not?
因为
Well, because
有很多人
we get a lot of
你知道  装变态毁了好多人
You know, they ruin it for everybody.
我知道
I know.
你知道  我昨晚穿那件喀什米尔毛衣去约会
You know, I wore that cashmere sweater on a date last night.
我离婚后第1次的约会
Oh. It was the first date since the divorce.
恭喜  你爱她吗
Well, congratulations. So do you love her?
她还不错  不过我也发现
No, no, no. She's nice, but, you know, it made me realize...
我还没有心情约会  你明白
...I'm just not ready to be dating, you know?
对
Huh.
这样
Well, uh...
真有意思
That's, uh... That's interesting.
那是什么  就是个防盗磁条
What was that? Oh, that's just an antitheft device.
那这是什么
Then what's this?
那个你也需要  因为很明显  贼会把它撕掉
Well, you need that too, because obviously a thief could just tear this up.
听着  今天晚上有个派对
Listen, we have to have a party tonight.
其实是5分钟后开始  所以大家都要取消别的计划
We have to have one in five minutes, so everybody cancel your plans.
你说什么  是啊  怎么回事
What? Yeah, what's going on?
我们要帮艾蜜莉搞个惊喜告别晚会
We have to have a surprise bon-voyage party for Emily.
其实是为了约书亚
But it's actually for Joshua.
他说他还没有心情约会
Look, he said he's not ready to date.
所以我得邀请他参加派对  才能在工作之外见到他
So I had to invite him to a party if I wanted to see him outside work.
现在我创造了个绝好的机会来勾引他
And now I have created the perfect opportunity to seduce him.
同样我也有机会见到约书亚  很想当面警告他
Well, as much as I'd like to meet Josh and warn him...
但是艾蜜莉和我不能参加  好吗
...Emily and I aren't gonna be here, all right?
她会来说声再见
She's gonna come by first to say goodbye.
我今晚还有个完整的计划  对不起  没戏唱了
And then I've got a whole special evening planned. So sorry. No party.
有人吗  惊喜
Hello? Surprise!
（欢送会）
惊喜  惊喜
Surprise!
从来没有人给我办过惊喜派对
No one's ever thrown me a surprise party before.
这都是罗斯的主意
Well, it was all Ross' idea.
你真好
You're so sweet.
我真的很惊喜啊
And I'm so surprised.
你真的没料到
You really didn't know?
约书亚在那边  你怎么在这边
Why are you over here if Joshua's all the way over there?
啊  因为我想玩玩欲擒故纵
Uh, because I'm trying to play hard-to-get.
快  快点他看过来了  说句好笑的话
Oh, quick. He's looking over here. Say something funny.
比如
Like what? Ha-ha-ha.
什么事这么好笑
What's so funny?
我说了个 "比如"
I said, "Like what?"
真深奥
Now that's a thinker.
你知道吗  玩欲擒故纵不好使啊
Okay, you know what? This playing-hard-to-get thing is not working.
把樱桃给我  好…
Uh, hand me those cherries. Okay.
好
Okay.
嗨
Hi. Hey.
要吃樱桃吗  不要  谢谢
Care for a cherry? No, thanks.
你知道吗  我可以用舌头把樱桃梗打结
You know, I can tie one of these into a knot using just my tongue.
你还好吗
You okay?
没事吧
You all right?
我们差不多得赶快走了
So we should probably get going soon.
但是派对才刚刚开始啊
Oh, but the party's only just getting started.
我们得在15分钟内   赶去"四季" 喝酒
Yeah, but we have to be at The Four Seasons for drinks in, oh, 15 minutes.
然后再去广场饭店吃晚饭
And then, uh, you know, then the Plaza for dinner.
那你为什么还在同一时间还办派对啊
So why did you plan a party at the same time?
不  不  不是的
No, no, no. Ha, ha.
其实  美国的惊喜派对时间都很短
Actually, American surprise parties are very short.
一般都是 "惊喜"   然后就 "我好惊喜  再见"
It's usually, "Surprise!" Then, "Oh, my God, I'm so surprised. Goodbye."
但是我觉得好好玩
Ross, I'm having such a great time.
你妹说你以前会假扮成老太太
Your sister has just been telling me that you used to dressed up like old ladies...
举办 "虚拟世界" 茶会
...and host make-believe tea parties.
摩妮卡说的  是吧
Monica said that, did she?
好赞  你接下来要放什么
Oh, yeah. Then what are you going to put on top of that?
放点蒜味肉肠  好棒
A little salami. Ooh, yeah. Yeah.
那蒜味肉肠上面呢
Then, um, what goes on top of the salami?
燻牛肉  太赞了
Pastrami. Oh, yeah.
你真是天才
You're a genius.
能帮我拉下拉链吗
Can someone give me a hand with the zipper.
往上拉
Up.
你换衣服  对  我需要我的幸运裙
You changed? Yeah, I just needed my lucky dress.
幸运是指露更多乳沟  对我管用
And "lucky" means "more cleavage"? Does for me.
你们看他啊  这么可爱
Oh, God, look at him. He's so cute.
我真想过去  抓着他  然后亲他
I just want to go over there and grab him and kiss him.
我怎么才能又亲他  又不让他知道我喜欢他
How could I kiss him without letting him know that I like him?
我知道怎么能办到  脱胸罩
Hey, I know how you can get him. Take off your bra.
什么
What?
在 "浑身是劲" 里   是"闪舞"里
There was a scene in Footloose... Flashdance.
对  那个水电女工  她是焊接工
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, with that plumber girl? She was a welder.
你在电影里吗
Were you, like, in the movie?
反正  她从衬衫里脱掉了胸罩
Anyway, she takes off her bra under the shirt...
然后从袖子里拉了出来
...and pulls it out the sleeve.
看着非常性感  还很有品位
Very sexy. And classy.
不然如果你想亲他  可以用槲寄生树（圣诞节传统  在槲寄生树下接吻）
Or if you wanna kiss him, um, you could use mistletoe.
现在不是圣诞节
It's not Christmas.
转瓶子  他不是小孩子了
Or spin the bottle. And he's not 11.
谢谢你们真用心  想的真周到
Thank you so much for this. It was really so thoughtful of you.
你们要走了
You're leaving?
对  我们还有别的事  我想我也要走了
Yes, we have something we have to get to. Uh, yeah, I think I'm gonna take off too.
先别走  留下来  你们得留下
No, you guys, you can't leave yet. You have to stay.
我们还准备了重头戏
We've got the whole big thing planned.
什么重头戏
What big thing?
像这样这么转瓶子
So, Spin-The-Bottle works like this.
我转瓶子
I spin the bottle.
指向阿甘  我就要亲阿甘
Lands on Gunther, so I would have to kiss Gunther.
就这样
All right.
谁要先
Who wants to go first?
我先
I'll go.
欢迎来到美国
Welcome to America.
好
All right.
天哪
Oh, my God.
连续两次  来个舌吻吧
Oh, my gosh. Two in a row. You gotta use your tongues now.
再来
All right.
这概率  太巧了
What are the odds? What are the odds?
够了  我们
Okay, that's enough, you know. Ha, ha.
让别人玩吧
Let's let someone else play.
你不想玩  干嘛来参加派对啊
Hey, if you didn't want to play, then why'd you come to the party?
好了  该我了
Okay, my turn.
是你
Oh! Look at that.
天哪
Oh, my God.
天哪  宝宝踢我了
Oh, my God. The baby just kicked.
没事  他踢了一次  还会踢第二次
It's okay, it's okay. If it kicked once, it'll kick again.
好吧  大家要记住刚才坐的位置
All right, well, everybody just remember where they were sitting.
有虫
It was a bug.
不管我多想吃
It doesn't matter how much I'm craving it.
你知道我为什么不吃肉  因为这是冷血谋杀
You know why I'm never gonna eat meat? Because it's cold-blooded murder.
好
Okay.
我的三明治上有菲比
There's a Phoebe on my sandwich.
菲比  你干什么
Phoebe, what are you doing?
我忍不住
I can't help it.
我要吃肉  孩子要吃肉
I need the meat. The baby needs the meat.
你知道和别人交往
You know how when you're dating someone...
绝对不能欺骗她们  除非遇见特惹火的
..and you don't want to cheat on them unless it's with someone really hot?
那当然  明白  这就对了
Yeah, totally. All right, okay.
吃肉也一样
Well, this is the same kind of deal.
如果你想犯错误
If you're gonna do something wrong...
就要错得漂亮
...do it right.
感觉好多了吗
Feel better?
对  但要付出多大代价
Yeah, but at what cost?
六个月   一天三顿肉
Six more months, three meals a day?
我会吃掉几百万头牛
I'm gonna eat like, you know, millions of cows.
要是我帮你扯平  肉方面
Hey, what if I said I could even things out for you, meat-wise?
什么  我很会吃肉  对吧
What? Well, I eat a lot of meat, right?
要是在孩子出生前
Yeah. But suppose, until the baby's born...
我戒吃肉
...I laid off it.
就不会多死动物   你是相当于在吃我的那份
No extra animals would die. You'd just be eating my animals.
你居然愿意为我这么做
Joey, I can't believe you'd do that for me.
当然愿意   我也可以吃素
Absolutely. I could be a vegetarian.
啤酒里没有肉  对吧
There's no meat in beer, right?
不要开胃菜  马上买单
Okay, we can still make dinner if we skip the appetizers...
还赶得上预定时间
...and ask for our check right away.
现在不能走  瑞秋要表演
We can't go now. Looks like Rachel is going to put on a skit.
我的天哪  你疯了吗
Oh, my God. Have you lost your mind?
不  不  我终于想通了
No, no, no. I am finally thinking clearly.
我的幸运裙没发挥作用
My lucky dress wasn't working out too well for me.
但这宝贝大学四年里  从没失手过
But for four years, this baby never missed.
瑞秋  等等  我不能让你…
Rachel, wait, I can't let...
其实  我也想看看会发生什么
Actually, I kind of want to see what happens.
嗨  嗨
Hey. Hey.
好棒的行头
Nice, uh, costume.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
我想给艾蜜莉  来个超级美式的告别表演
Well, I wanted to give Emily a big American goodbye cheer.
太棒了
So okay. Whoo!
预备  起
Ready. Okay.
给我个E  E
Give me an "E." GROUP: E.
给我个M  M
Give me an "M." GROUP: M.
给我个I  I
Give me an "I." GROUP: I.
给我个L  L
Give me an "L." GROUP: L.
给我个Y  Y
Give me a "Y." GROUP: Y.
拼起来是什么
What do you get?
哦  艾蜜莉
Oh! Emily.
哇  艾蜜莉
Whoo! Emily.
我这拉拉队长怎么样
Okay. That's me as a cheerleader. Ta-da!
你没事吧  有颗牙齿松了
You all right? I just loosened a tooth.
小意思  我有牙医
It's no big deal. I have a dentist, you know?
我敷点冰块  失陪
I'm gonna go put some ice on it. Excuse me.
我做得怎么样  怎么样  我认为你成功了
What do I do now? What do I do now? I think you're done.
该脱胸罩了
Okay, time to take off the bra.
刚才表演很精彩
Uh, that was really great.
但我真得走了
But I got to take off, actually.
脱胸罩
Take the bra off.
好吧  过来  我陪你去拿外套
All right, come on, let's go get your coat.
好的
Okay.
瑞秋是我的女朋友
Rachel's my girlfriend.
今晚真的很开心的
So this was really fun.
是啊  很开心
Oh, yeah, it was real fun.
你知道  这胸罩
You know, this bra...
真的很不舒服
...is really bothering me.
这里曾经是我的睡房
You know, this used to be my bedroom.
嗯
Yeah.
有很多回忆  很多很多回忆
A lot of memories in here. Lot of memories.
要是墙壁能说话  你知道  它们会说什么吗
If these walls could talk, you know what they'd say?
"想回忆往事吗"
"Want to hear some memories?"
你需要帮忙吗
Need a...? Need a little hand there?
不  不用  没问题  我应付的了
Oh, no, no, no. No, I got this all under control.
可你看起来不像能应付的了
You really don't seem like you do.
算了啦   真是
God. Forget it! Oh, this is...
事情本来不该这样的
This is not how this was supposed to happen.
那应该怎样啊
What was supposed to happen?
我说的时候你能不看我吗
Can you not look at me when I say this?
我以为只要能把你找来
I thought that if I could get you here...
就可以勾引你
...I could seduce you.
我上班不穿西装
Uh, I don't wear suits to work...
却从你那买了六套
...and I bought six of them from you.
抱歉啊   我以为你有需要
Well, I'm sorry. I thought you needed them.
我意思是  我不停地来找你  是因为我想见你
My point is, I kept coming back because I wanted to see you.
为什么  因为我喜欢你
Why? Because I like you.
你喜欢我
You like me?
是啊
Yeah.
你漂亮  聪明又成熟
I mean, you're beautiful and smart and sophisticated.
这些印象不都是来自今晚
A lot of this isn't, you know, based on tonight.
但是你喜欢我
But you like me?
天啊  这段日子以来  我们竟然互相喜欢
Oh, my God. I can't believe this. All this time, I liked you and you liked me.
啊
Oh!
但是  不要说 "但是"
But... No don't say "but."
"但是" 都没好事  停在 "我们互相喜欢"就好
"But" is never good. Let's leave it at "I like you and you like me."
好
Okay, uh...
然而  那是好听的 "但是"
However... No, that's a fancy "but."
我刚结束我的婚姻
My marriage, like, just ended.
我还没心情跟别人交往
And I'm really not ready to get into anything yet.
但是…
But...
对不起  我需要点时间
I'm sorry. I just need a little time.
好啊
Okay.
你在这里  我刚才在找你
Oh, there you are. I was looking for you before.
约书亚走了  你和艾蜜莉也可以走了
Joshua's gone, so you and Emily are free to go.
无所谓
It's okay.
她还在里面享受这场假派对呢
She's still in there enjoying her fake party.
现在我要做什么也来不及了
And, uh, it's too late to do any of the stuff I had planned, so...
罗斯
Ross.
抱歉  我毁了你美好的夜晚
I'm sorry. I completely ruined your evening.
是啊
Ahem. Yeah.
如果这让你好受点  我出了个大丑
Well, if it makes you feel any better, I made a fool of myself.
你有没有高兴点
Helps a little.
有地方让悲惨的衰仔坐一坐吗
Is there a room on that step for a pathetic loser?
过来  坐吧
Yeah, have a seat.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
反正只是一段两星期的恋情
I mean, it was just a two-week thing anyway.
我只是不想以这样的方式结束  你知道
I just didn't want it to end this way, you know.
也许你不想结束呢
Or maybe you didn't want it to end?
什么意思
What do you mean?
看起来你很喜欢她
You seem to really like her.
没错  真的是
Yeah, I really do.
但我能做什么呢
Yeah, but what am I gonna do?
我们说好了只在一起两个星期
We both agreed it was gonna be a two-week thing.
你知道  双方没有责任
You know? No commitment.
罗斯
Ross?
那个女孩整晚都跟你的朋友聊天
That girl just spent the entire evening talking to your friends...
吵着要听你的事
...asking to hear stories about you...
还拿摩妮卡的相册来看
...looking through Monica's photo albums.
我意思是  你不会为了两周的交往而做这些
I mean, you don't do that if you're just in it for two weeks.
你这么想
You think?
是的  到她上飞机前你还有14个小时
You've got, like, 14 hours until she has to be at the airport.
你却坐在走廊上
And you're sitting here in a hallway...
陪一个28岁  嘴肿起来的啦啦队长
...with a 28-year-old cheerleader with a fat lip.
你说得对
Hey, you're right. Yeah.
谢了
Thanks.
哪本相簿
What photo album was it?
不知道   是你和一群白化病孩子
I don't know. It was you and a bunch of albino kids.
天啊  他们不是白化病
Oh, my God. Those weren't albino kids.
那是电脑夏令营啦
That was computer camp. Rach.
嗨   嗨
Hey. Hey.
你是个悲惨的衰仔吧  对  就是我
You're a pathetic loser, right? Oh, yeah.
坐
Sit.
嗨
Hi.
天哪   约书亚
Oh, my God. Joshua.
其实
Look.
所有我刚才说的没心情的话
All those things I said about not being ready...
都不是真的  不  都是真的
They're not true? No, they're all true.
哦
Oh.
但是…
But...
哦
Oh.
我喜欢这个 "但是"
Oh, I love that "but."
要不要进去喝杯咖啡
Um, do you want to go inside and get some coffee?
好啊
Yeah. Okay.
从未失手
Every time.
你放什么  燻牛肉
Ooh, what do you got there? Pastrami.
赞
Yeah.
你知道什么跟它最配  腌牛肉
Hey, you know what goes good with that? Mm-hm. Corned beef.
我想说红肠  但腌牛肉更棒
Ooh, I was going to say bologna. But that's better.
要不要放点燻火鸡肉  好
How about a little of that smoked turkey? Okay.
妈呀
Oh, Mama.
孩子什么时候生啊  半年后
When is the baby due? Six months.
如果是自然死亡的牛
Hey, now, if a cow should die of natural causes...
我就可以吃  是吗
...I could have one of those, right?
我会先下手
Not if I get there first.